JAZIEL ENRIQUEZ (JAZZ)

Contact info:

Email: jazielenriquez@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/yourfellajazz

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jazielenriquez/

Online Portfolio: https://jenriquezportfolio.netlify.app/

Phone: 915-888-5233

PROFILE SUMMARY

Proficient in problem solving in hardware and software. Committed to apply my skills in Javascript, React, and psychology. Experience learning and applying skills in front end development via open source and personal projects. Experience in maintaining high standards and caring for others. Self-led learner and excellent at problem-solving. Volunteer experience in serving others with their social, developmental, and organizational skills. Effective in utilizing interpersonal skills and connecting with others in the workplace to communicate effectively and better perform assigned duties and tasks.

| Google IT Support certification | Bilingual | React.js | JavaScript | Node.js | Bootstrap | jQuery | Redux | HTTP/JSON/AJAX | GIT | HTML | CSS/SCSS | SQL | tailwind | NPM | Sales/Customer service experience |

EXPERIENCE/CERTIFICATIONS

Tech Certifications

Google IT Support Professional Certificate — a six month IT support program that covers troubleshooting, customer service, networking, operating systems, system administration, and security, and includes hands-on labs.

Solo learn - Advanced HTML, CSS & Javascript Certifications.

Online Portfolio

Personalized code to create a simple yet modern portfolio. All personal projects, info, and links can be found here. One page layout and fully responsive. Dynamic website optimized with Parcel, Bootstrap 4, SCSS, and Javascript. Used Github and Netlify to host website online.

Link: https://jenriquezportfolio.netlify.app/

Verse generator

Generates a new verse with every click and can be tweeted. Built with font awesome

icons, custom google fonts, custom background patterns, styled components, and Javascript.

Mobile responsive. Used DOM manipulation. Fetch's data with local array but code is easily

modifiable to add asynchronous code with API to fetch data if needed.

Link: https://yourfellajazz.github.io/verse-generator/

Light-Dark Mode

Built with custom fonts, custom background, styled buttons, Redux and Javascript. Used

event listeners, DOM manipulation, and dynamic functions. Used local storage to store theme

data. Code can be simplified to one function instead of two for a cleaner look. (Shown in Github

JavaScript file)

Link: https://yourfellajazz.github.io/light-darkmode/

Animated Template

Single page HTML website with inline JavaScript and Tailwind CSS. Built and modified

website with Creative Tim. Cleaned and reduced original HTML code for easier modification.

Integrated font awesome icons and custom images. While this website was being built, the main

lesson learned was to know when to use async or defer methods in Javascript. Since the third

party Javascript animation to scroll was inside the HTML, the loading time of the website was a

priority.

Link: https://yourfellajazz.github.io/history-of-the-web-/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EDUCATOR - LULULEMON - 2022-2023

Responsibilities:

Communicated and developed relationships effectively with all my co-workers to create a

smooth and better workplace for the company and for my role.

Took initiative to greet and know the customers in order to better suit their needs of coming into the store. Introduced myself and gave information about the product they

were interested in while also providing other options if needed.

Adapted to any role that was asked of me to do and asked questions if needed in order to

perform my task better.

Assisted customers by asking open-ended questions rather than plain questions.

Maintained a positive, encouraging, and friendly attitude by introducing myself not only to guests but to new co-workers.

Contributed to revenue increase each month by increasing item per transaction sales and offering exchanges to customers instead of returns.

Initiated the possibility of new customers through referrals.

Worked independently and used problem solving skills when it came to customer questions and concerns.

HOSPITALITY TEAM MEMBER - CHICK-FIL-A - 2021-2022

Responsibilities:

Provided and maintained high-standard customer service in a fast-paced environment by mastering tasks for handling currency transactions, order taking, stocking, and inventory control.

Communicated clearly with customers and co-workers and maintained a positive, friendly, and welcoming attitude.

Resolved complaints quickly, professionally, and kindly.

Adapted to different roles in my position quickly and effectively.

Developed good relationships with customers that influenced them to come back and recognize my service to them.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT EL PASO – BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN PSYCHOLOGY, 2022

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Youth ministry

Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2015-2017

Responsibilities: Motivated, lead, and organized a group of 60 kids every Sunday and Wednesday in order to develop and help their personal growth, skills, and maturity.

Young adult ministry

Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2021-2022

Responsibilities: Communicated and worked together effectively in a group. Organized, lead, managed, and applied interpersonal communication skills in order to encourage and uplift college students to grow in their self-esteem, mental health, and emotional state.

Food giveaway

Abundant Living Faith Center, El Paso, TX 2020

Responsibilities: Teamed up with other people in order to serve the community and help those in need during the COVID-19 pandemic. Loaded food and drinks into vehicles and distributed to those in need.

Hospitality Member

Shoreline City, Dallas, TX 2023

Responsibilities: Encouraged and greeted new people. Initiated and introduced myself to new people in order to connect with them and build genuine relationships. Worked together with others to make new people feel welcomed and known.